<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >
<channel>
  <title>Economia e Mercati - Proiezioni di Borsa</title>
  <atom:link href="https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/category/economia-e-mercati/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <link>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it</link>
  <description></description>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2023 13:17:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <language>it-IT</language>
  <sy:updatePeriod>
  hourly  </sy:updatePeriod>
  <sy:updateFrequency>
  1 </sy:updateFrequency>
  <generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>
<image>
  <url>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/cropped-pdb-fav-2020-32x32.png</url>
  <title>Economia e Mercati - Proiezioni di Borsa</title>
  <link>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it</link>
  <width>32</width>
  <height>32</height>
</image>
  <item>
           <title>
NVIDIA and affiliates partner to advance quantum computing technology
           </title>   
           <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:13:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>1</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>
NVIDIA partners with Jülich Supercomputing Centre and Partec to establish a quantum computing lab
     </li>
            <li>
NVIDIA, Rolls-Royce, and Classiq achieve breakthrough in quantum computing for computational fluid dynamics in jet engines
     </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
NVIDIA has teamed up with Jülich Supercomputing Centre and Partec to establish a quantum computing lab. The lab will concentrate on creating quantum algorithms and software for scientific and industrial purposes. Quantum computing has the ability to solve complicated problems that conventional computing cannot.
     </p>
            <p>
In a separate partnership, NVIDIA, Rolls-Royce, and Classiq have achieved a significant breakthrough in quantum computing for computational fluid dynamics in jet engines. This breakthrough has the potential to transform the aerospace industry.
     </p> 
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:NVDA</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>   
  
  <item>
           <title>
Twitter CEO Elon Musk emphasizes need to hire and rehire employees for software advancement
           </title>   
           <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:11:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>2</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>
Twitter needs to focus on improving its software to remain competitive in the market
     </li>            
            </ul>
            <p>
In a recent CNBC interview, Elon Musk, the CEO of Twitter, emphasized the need for the company to hire and rehire employees to advance its software. He also acknowledged that Twitter is currently an advertising business. As such, the company needs to focus on improving its software to remain competitive in the market. Musk's comments highlight the importance of investing in technology and innovation to stay ahead of the curve. By prioritizing software development, Twitter can continue to evolve and meet the changing needs of its users.
     </p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:TWTR</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>   
<item>
           <title>Microsoft CEO clarifies OpenAI's control and involvement</title>   
           <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 05:45:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>3</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>OpenAI is controlled by a nonprofit board</li>            
            <li>Microsoft has a noncontrolling interest in OpenAI</li>
            </ul>
            <p>Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella clarified during a congressional hearing on AI regulation that OpenAI is controlled by a nonprofit board and that Microsoft has a noncontrolling interest in the organization. The hearing discussed potential frameworks for regulation, including safety standards and licensing and testing requirements for AI models. OpenAI CEO Sam Altman testified on the need for regulatory intervention in the emerging industry of artificial intelligence.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:MSFT</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>   
       
<item>
           <title>Mizuho Adjusts Alibaba's Price Target to $145</title>   
           <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 06:14:24 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>4</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>Mizuho adjusts Alibaba's price target to $145</li>            
            <li>Alibaba's stock price closed at $82.22, down 1.31%</li>
            <li>Alibaba is trading at a discount compared to its industry's average Forward P/E of 20.36</li>
            </ul>
            <p>Alibaba's stock price closed at $82.22, down 1.31% from the previous trading session. Mizuho has adjusted Alibaba's price target to $145 from $155, while maintaining a buy rating for the company. The company is expected to post earnings of $1.30 per share for the current quarter.</p>
            <p>Alibaba is graded A on valuation metrics, indicating that it is trading at a discount to its peers. It is currently holding a Zacks Rank of #3 (Hold), and is trading at a Forward P/E ratio of 10.17, which is a discount compared to its industry's average Forward P/E of 20.36.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:BABA</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>

<item>
           <title>AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc expects box-office sales despite competition from streaming services</title>   
           <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:16:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>5</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc optimistic about box-office sales</li>            
            <li>Independent film companies could fulfil unmet appetite of theatre audiences</li> 
            <li>Apple Inc to premiere 'Killers of the Flower Moon' at Cannes before global streaming release in October</li> 
            </ul>
            <p>AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc and its affiliates remain hopeful about the box-office sales of upcoming movies, despite competition from streaming services. Independent film companies are also optimistic at Cannes, as they offer something different to theatre audiences. However, buyers are being cautious due to the unstable global economy. Traditional film companies are facing tough competition to increase subscriber numbers as they have joined the streaming revolution. Apple Inc will premiere Martin Scorsese's 'Killers of the Flower Moon' at Cannes and has partnered with Paramount to release the film in theatres before streaming it globally in October.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:AMC</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>
       
       <item>
           <title>Meta Platforms Inc Advances AI Infrastructure with Custom Accelerator Chip and Next-Gen Data Center</title>   
           <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 04:15:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>6</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>Meta Platforms Inc is advancing their AI infrastructure with a new data center design optimized for AI and a custom silicon chip for AI recommendation systems</li>            
            <li>Meta also built 'CodeCompose', a generative AI coding assistant to help its engineers write code</li>
            <li>The company's longer-term goal is to build more AI tools to support teams across the whole software development process and to open source more of its generative AI coding tools.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>Meta Platforms Inc, the parent company of Facebook, has made significant advancements in their AI infrastructure. Mark Zuckerberg, CEO of Meta Platforms Inc, shared an update on the company's next-generation infrastructure for AI in a Facebook post. Meta has a new data center design optimized for AI, equipped to support liquid cooling hardware to handle training and inference at large scale. The company also designed a custom silicon chip, called 'Meta Training and Inference Accelerator', to power its AI recommendation systems. Additionally, Meta built 'CodeCompose', a generative AI coding assistant to help its engineers write code. The company's longer-term goal is to build more AI tools to support teams across the whole software development process and to open source more of its generative AI coding tools. This news caused a 1% rise in the company's shares.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:META</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>

<item>
           <title>Netflix predicted to outperform rivals with ad-supported tier</title>   
           <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 04:14:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>7</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>Netflix expected to see growth with ad-supported tier</li>            
            <li>BofA survey shows willingness to pay for password sharing and switch to ad-supported tier</li>
            <li>Wedbush predicts Netflix can exceed free cash flow guidance</li>
            </ul>
            <p>According to BofA Securities and Wedbush Securities, Netflix is expected to continue its growth and outperform competitors with its ad-supported tier. BofA's survey revealed that many households are willing to pay for password sharing and switch to the ad-supported tier, which is expected to be a major driver of growth for the company. Wedbush predicts that Netflix can exceed its free cash flow guidance by balancing viewership levels with ad costs and ad views per hour. Despite facing challenges in 2023, both firms maintain a positive outlook on Netflix's future and reiterate their buy and outperform ratings, respectively.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:NFLX</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>
       
       <item>
           <title>Amazon's Strong Performance in 2023</title>   
           <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 02:15:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>8</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>Amazon is a market leader in several business segments</li>            
            <li>Amazon's ad business is its fastest-growing segment</li>
            <li>Investors remain bullish on AMZN with a mean price target of $142.16</li>
            </ul>
            <p>Amazon's stock has surged in 2023, as the company dominates various business segments such as online sales, cloud infrastructure, digital advertising, and streaming. In 2022, the company reported sales of $513.9 billion, with 60% of unit sales coming from its third-party seller ecosystem. Amazon's ad business is its fastest-growing segment, with a high return on ad spending leading to impressive top-line growth. Despite an expected slowdown in revenue growth, Amazon is well-positioned to benefit from multiple secular tailwinds, including the potential for growth in online sales and cloud spending. Investors are optimistic about AMZN, with a mean price target of $142.16, representing a 23% increase from the current trading price.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:AMZN</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>

<item>
           <title>Third Point LLC acquires 1 million shares in AMD, boosting stock prices</title>   
           <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>9</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>AMD's stock prices increase by 5.2%</li>            
            </ul>
            <p>Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) saw a 5.2% increase in its shares to $102.42 after Third Point LLC, owned by Daniel Loeb, acquired a stake of 1 million shares in the company. This comes after a loss in the first quarter caused AMD's stock to fall by more than 9% on May 3. However, shares recovered the next day after a Bloomberg report revealed that AMD will work with Microsoft to develop artificial intelligence processors. As a result, AMD is currently the top gainer in the S&P 500.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:AMD</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>
       
       <item>
           <title>Tesla considers setting up manufacturing plant in India</title>   
           <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 01:15:28 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>10</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>Tesla is exploring the possibility of setting up a manufacturing plant in India</li>            
            <li>The proposed plant would produce electric vehicles for both domestic sales and exports</li>            
            </ul>
            <p>Tesla is exploring the possibility of establishing a new manufacturing facility in India to increase its market share in the country. The proposed plant would produce electric vehicles for both domestic sales and exports. Tesla executives are currently in India to discuss local sourcing of parts and other matters with the government. Talks with India on reducing import taxes on cars stalled last year, but Tesla's renewed interest in the country comes almost a year after it suspended plans to sell cars there.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:TSLA</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>

<item>
           <title>Apple's App Store Prevents Over $2 Billion in Fraudulent Transactions in 2022</title>   
           <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:15:29 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>11</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>The App Store rejected nearly 1.7 million app submissions for failing to meet standards for privacy, security, and content.</li>            
            </ul>
            <p>Apple Inc has announced that its App Store prevented over $2 billion in potentially fraudulent transactions in 2022. The company also disabled over 282 million customer accounts associated with fraudulent and abusive activity. Furthermore, the App Store rejected nearly 1.7 million app submissions for failing to meet standards for privacy, security, and content. In the last 30 days, Apple blocked close to 3.9 million attempts to install or launch apps distributed illicitly through the Developer Enterprise Program.
</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:AAPL</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>
       
      <item>
           <title>Google Settles with Texas Attorney General Over Deceptive Pixel 4 Ads</title>   
           <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 04:15:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>12</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>State claimed Google hired DJs to share personal experiences with phone, but refused to offer them a phone for use</li>            
            <li>Google states they take compliance with advertising laws seriously and have processes in place to ensure they follow relevant regulations and industry standards</li>
            </ul>
            <p>Google has settled with Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton for $8 million over misleading advertisements for the Pixel 4 smartphone. The state accused Google of hiring DJs to promote the phone without providing them with a phone to use. Google has emphasized their commitment to complying with advertising laws and adhering to industry standards. They have implemented processes to ensure they meet these requirements.</p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:GOOGL</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
