<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
  xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
  xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
  >
<channel>
  <title>Economia e Mercati - Proiezioni di Borsa</title>
  <atom:link href="https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/category/economia-e-mercati/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <link>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it</link>
  <description></description>
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2023 13:17:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
  <language>it-IT</language>
  <sy:updatePeriod>
  hourly  </sy:updatePeriod>
  <sy:updateFrequency>
  1 </sy:updateFrequency>
  <generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>
<image>
  <url>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/cropped-pdb-fav-2020-32x32.png</url>
  <title>Economia e Mercati - Proiezioni di Borsa</title>
  <link>https://www.proiezionidiborsa.it</link>
  <width>32</width>
  <height>32</height>
</image>
  <item>
           <title>
NVIDIA and affiliates partner to advance quantum computing technology
           </title>   
           <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:15:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>1</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>
NVIDIA partners with Jülich Supercomputing Centre and Partec to establish a quantum computing lab
     </li>
            <li>
NVIDIA, Rolls-Royce, and Classiq achieve breakthrough in quantum computing for computational fluid dynamics in jet engines
     </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
NVIDIA has teamed up with Jülich Supercomputing Centre and Partec to establish a quantum computing lab. The lab will concentrate on creating quantum algorithms and software for scientific and industrial purposes. Quantum computing has the ability to solve complicated problems that conventional computing cannot.
     </p>
            <p>
In a separate partnership, NVIDIA, Rolls-Royce, and Classiq have achieved a significant breakthrough in quantum computing for computational fluid dynamics in jet engines. This breakthrough has the potential to transform the aerospace industry.
     </p> 
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NASDAQ:NVDA</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>   
  
  <item>
           <title>
Twitter CEO Elon Musk emphasizes need to hire and rehire employees for software advancement
           </title>   
           <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 00:15:20 +0000</pubDate>       
           <guid>2</guid>
           <description>
           <ul>
            <li>
Twitter needs to focus on improving its software to remain competitive in the market
     </li>            
            </ul>
            <p>
In a recent CNBC interview, Elon Musk, the CEO of Twitter, emphasized the need for the company to hire and rehire employees to advance its software. He also acknowledged that Twitter is currently an advertising business. As such, the company needs to focus on improving its software to remain competitive in the market. Musk's comments highlight the importance of investing in technology and innovation to stay ahead of the curve. By prioritizing software development, Twitter can continue to evolve and meet the changing needs of its users.
     </p>
           </description> 
           <category domain="tradingview:symbol">NYSE:TWTR</category> 	      
           <category domain="tradingview:language">en</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:urgency">2</category>
           <category domain="tradingview:isExclusive">true</category>   
       </item>   


  </channel>
</rss>
